Guide to the Henry Knox Sherrill Family Papers
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Sermons, Writings, 1914-1972, n.d.; Series II
  - 1952 Jan-Jun
    - Message for WBS, 1952 Jan 17 (Box 18, Folder 444)
    - Endorsement of American Cancer Society, 1952 Feb 19 (Box 18, Folder 444)
    - Statement re: juvenile delinquency, 1952 Feb 19 (Box 18, Folder 444)
    - Easter message for the Spokesman-Review, Spokane, WA, 1952 Mar 13 (Box 18, Folder 444)
    - Easter message ( Journal American ), 1952 Mar 25 (Box 18, Folder 444)
    - Easter message ( The Outlook ), 1952 Mar (Box 18, Folder 444)
    - Address at Yale University, 1952 Apr 1 (Box 18, Folder 444)
    - Easter greeting to the Armed Forces, 1952 Apr 1 (Box 18, Folder 444)
    - Easter message for the NCCC, 1952 Apr 12 (Box 18, Folder 444)
    - Easter message ( Forth ), 1952 Apr 13 (Box 18, Folder 444)
    - Message re: General Convention, 1952 Jun 2 (Box 18, Folder 444)
    - Commencement Address, Union College, 1952 Jun 8 (Box 18, Folder 444)
    - Message re: RSV publication, 1952 Jun 18 (Box 18, Folder 444)
    - Message, 1952 Jun 19 (Box 18, Folder 444)
  - 1952 Jul-Dec
    - "Greeting to the People of Czecho- slovakia on John Hus Day" Message re: NCCC Biennial Assembly 1952 Jul g, 1952 Jul 6 (Box 18, Folder 445)
    - "Education for Today's World" ( The Churchman ), 1952 Aug (Box 18, Folder 445)
    - Opening address: 57th General Convention ( The Living Church, 1952 Sep 14; The Witness, 1952 Sep 18; Forth, 1952 Oct), 1952 Sep 26 (Box 18, Folder 445)
    - Endorsement of Community Chest Campaign, 1952 Sep 26 (Box 18, Folder 445)
    - Message re: importance of voting, 1952 Oct 1 (Box 18, Folder 445)
    - Christmas message for Forth, 1952 Oct 15 (Box 18, Folder 445)
    - Message re: Crusade for Freedom, 1952 Oct 17 (Box 18, Folder 445)
    - Sermon, 1952 Oct 19 (Box 18, Folder 445)
    - Message, 1952 Nov 3 (Box 18, Folder 445)
    - Sermon, 1952 Nov 11 (Box 18, Folder 445)
    - Statement re: Slansky trials in Czechoslovakia, 1952 Nov 23 (Box 18, Folder 445)
    - Address to NCCC Biennial Meeting, 1952 Dec 9 (Box 18, Folder 445)
  - 1953
    - Message from NCCC, 1953 Feb 12 (Box 18, Folder 446)
    - Memorial for Rev. Dr. James Thayer Addison, 1953 Feb 26 (Box 18, Folder 446)
    - Easter message, 1953 Apr 5 (Box 18, Folder 446)
    - Message, 1953 Apr 17 (Box 18, Folder 446)
    - Statement on meaning of freedom, 1953 Jun 2 (Box 18, Folder 446)
    - Address, Hamilton College, 1953 Jun 14 (Box 18, Folder 446)
    - Foreword to Dr. Addison's book, 1953 Jun 23 (Box 18, Folder 446)
    - Armistice message, 1953 Jul 27 (Box 18, Folder 446)
    - Greeting to The American Hebrew, 1953 Aug 3 (Box 18, Folder 446)
    - Greeting to the choir of St. Paul's Church, London, 1953 Aug 3 (Box 18, Folder 446)
    - Address to the America-Japan Society, 1953 Sep-Oct (Box 18, Folder 446)
    - Notes for TV recording, 1953 Oct 9 (Box 18, Folder 446)
    - Message re: the UN ( Redbook ), 1953 Oct (Box 18, Folder 446)
    - Message to Yale and Harvard, 1953 Nov 21 (Box 18, Folder 446)
    - Christmas message to Radio Free Europe, 1953 Dec 1 (Box 18, Folder 446)
  - 1954 Jan-Jun
    - Address to the Association of American Colleges, 1954 Jan 12 (Box 18, Folder 447)
    - Foreword to the Annual Report of the National Council for 1953, 1954 Jan 24 (Box 18, Folder 447)
    - Message; Review of Ethics in a Business Society by Marquis W. Childs, 1954 Feb 23 (Box 18, Folder 447)
    - Foreword for Go Preach, 1954 Mar 12 (Box 18, Folder 447)
    - Message re: Samuel McCrea Cavert Fund, 1954 Mar 15 (Box 18, Folder 447)
    - "Builders for Christ", 1954 Mar 30 (Box 18, Folder 447)
    - Easter message ( Forth ), 1954 Apr (Box 18, Folder 447)
    - Commencement address, Wheaton College ( The Witness, 1954 Jun 24), 1954 Jun 6 (Box 18, Folder 447)
    - Baccalaureate address, Norwich Univ., 1954 Jun 13 (Box 18, Folder 447)
    - "An Appreciation of Hughell Edgar Woodall Fosbroke", 1954 Jun (Box 18, Folder 447)
  - 1954 Aug-Dec
    - Opening address to the Anglican Congress, 1954 Aug 4 (Box 18, Folder 448)
    - Message, 1954 Sep 21 (Box 18, Folder 448)
    - Christmas message, 1954 Oct 18 (Box 18, Folder 448)
    - Address to Berkeley Divinity School, 1954 Oct 26 (Box 18, Folder 448)
    - Address for YWCA Centennial, 1954 Nov 7 (Box 18, Folder 448)
    - Message on Bingo for Newsweek, 1954 Nov 8 (Box 18, Folder 448)
    - Greeting to dinner in support of UN, 1954 Nov 9 (Box 18, Folder 448)
    - Christmas message for Bank Notes, 1954 Nov 10 (Box 18, Folder 448)
    - Foreword to Dr. Heuss's book, 1954 Dec 16 (Box 18, Folder 448)
    - Christmas message ( Forth ), 1954 Dec (Box 18, Folder 448)
    - "Answers for an Agnostic", ca. 1954 (Box 18, Folder 448)
  - 1955
    - Message re: the Forward Movement, 1955 Jan 4 (Box 18, Folder 449)
    - Greeting to World Council, 1955 Jan 19 (Box 18, Folder 449)
    - Foreword to 1954 Report, National Council, 1955 Jan 19 (Box 18, Folder 449)
    - Easter message, 1955 Feb 9 (Box 18, Folder 449)
    - Easter message for Radio Free Europe, 1955 Mar 8 (Box 18, Folder 449)
    - Message, 1955 Mar 11 (Box 18, Folder 449)
    - Message for Spotlight Magazine, 1955 Mar 17 (Box 18, Folder 449)
    - Message to World Council, 1955 May 4 (Box 18, Folder 449)
    - Commencement address, Kent School, 1955 Jun 2 (Box 18, Folder 449)
    - Statement re: National Council program, 1955 Jul 27 (Box 18, Folder 449)
    - Message re: World Council, 1955 Aug 22 (Box 18, Folder 449)
    - Sermon to youth, 1955 Aug 28 (Box 18, Folder 449)
    - General Convention address, 1955 Sep 4 (Box 18, Folder 449)
    - Statement on Civil Defense, 1955 Oct (Box 18, Folder 449)
    - Address in Australia, 1955 Oct (Box 18, Folder 449)
    - Message re: National Council, 1955 Nov 1 (Box 18, Folder 449)
    - Message for Better Homes and Gardens, 1955 Nov 22 (Box 18, Folder 449)
    - Message re: General Convention, 1955 Dec 12 (Box 18, Folder 449)
    - Christmas message, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 449)
  - 1956
    - Foreword for National Council Report, 1956 Jan 11 (Box 18, Folder 450)
    - Lenten message, 1956 Jan 13 (Box 18, Folder 450)
    - Address to Ohio Pastors' Conference, 1956 Jan 13 (Box 18, Folder 450)
    - Appeal for contributions to World Council, 1956 Feb 24 (Box 18, Folder 450)
    - Message re: visit to Russia, 1956 Apr 3 (Box 18, Folder 450)
    - Message for the Church Times, London, 1956 Apr 11 (Box 18, Folder 450)
    - Message for Every Member Canvass, 1956 Apr (Box 18, Folder 450)
    - Address at installation of the Rt. Rev. Hamilton West (excerpts), 1956 May (Box 18, Folder 450)
    - Address at anniversary of St. Paul's School, Concord, NH, 1956 Jun 3 (Box 18, Folder 450)
    - Baccalaureate sermon, Lehigh University, 1956 Jun 17 (Box 18, Folder 450)
    - Appeal for contributions to Builders for Christ, 1956 Jun 21 (Box 18, Folder 450)
    - Foreword to Window on Japan by Miss Lea, 1956 Jul 23 (Box 18, Folder 450)
    - Statement on Juvenile delinquency, 1956 Sep 13 (Box 18, Folder 450)
    - Introduction to the Manual of the Daughters of the King, 1956 Sep 13 (Box 18, Folder 450)
    - Christmas message, 1956 Sep 18 (Box 18, Folder 450)
    - Foreword to Dean Fosbroke's Good Friday Meditations, 1956 Sep 18 (Box 18, Folder 450)
    - Congratulatory message, 1956 Sep 27 (Box 18, Folder 450)
    - Greetings to Australia, 1956 Sep 28 (Box 18, Folder 450)
    - Statement for booklet on church school missionary offering, 1956 Oct 24 (Box 18, Folder 450)
    - Endorsement of the Order of Sir Galahad, 1956 Dec 5 (Box 18, Folder 450)
    - Appeal for funds for refugee program, 1956 Dec 14 (Box 18, Folder 450)
  - 1957 Jan-Jun
    - Review of The Church in Soviet Russia by Matthew Spinka, 1957 Jan 18 (Box 18, Folder 451)
    - Introduction to Russian film, 1957 Jan 18 (Box 18, Folder 451)
    - Annual Report, National Council, 1956, 1957 Jan 22 (Box 18, Folder 451)
    - Message re: Bishop Parsons, 1957 Jan 30 (Box 18, Folder 451)
    - Statement for Report of the Delegation to South India, 1957 Feb 13 (Box 18, Folder 451)
    - Message in praise of Bishop Binsted, 1957 Mar 7 (Box 18, Folder 451)
    - Greeting to conference at Berchtesgaden, 1957 Apr 15 (Box 18, Folder 451)
    - "Commendatory Preface" for the Pan-Anglican, 1957 Apr 18 (Box 18, Folder 451)
    - Message, 1957 Apr 18 (Box 18, Folder 451)
    - Address at Jamestown, 350th anniversary, 1957 Apr 26 (Box 18, Folder 451)
    - Broadcast sermon, 1957 May 12 (Box 18, Folder 451)
    - Sermon, 1957 Jun 6 (Box 18, Folder 451)
    - Commendation of the General Theological Seminary, 1957 Jun 17 (Box 18, Folder 451)
  - 1957 Sep-Dec
    - Address at Washington Cathedral, 1957 Sep 28 (Box 18, Folder 452)
    - Endorsement of the Order of Sir Galahad, 1957 Oct 16 (Box 18, Folder 452)
    - Centennial address, Philadelphia Divinity School ( The Living Church, Nov 3), 1957 Oct 23 (Box 18, Folder 452)
    - Whitsunday message for offering envelopes, 1957 Oct 31 (Box 18, Folder 452)
    - Commendation of the Church Society for College Work, 1957 Oct 23 (Box 18, Folder 452)
    - Greeting to the Girls Friendly Society, 1957 Nov 2 (Box 18, Folder 452)
    - Address to General Assembly of the NCCC, 1957 Dec 5 (Box 18, Folder 452)
    - Christmas message ( Forth ), 1957 Dec (Box 18, Folder 452)
  - 1958-1959
    - Annual report, National Council, 1957, 1958 Jan 23 (Box 19, Folder 453)
    - Easter message ( The Living Church, 1958 Apr 6), 1958 Jan 23 (Box 19, Folder 453)
    - Preface for "Prayers for Christian Healing" by the Rev. Albert Campion, 1958 Feb 11 (Box 19, Folder 453)
    - Easter sermon, 1958 Apr 6 (Box 19, Folder 453)
    - Appeal for Every Member Canvass, 1958 Apr 10 (Box 19, Folder 453)
    - Announcement of General Convention, 1958 Jun 6 (Box 19, Folder 453)
    - Announcement of nation-wide corporate communion, 1958 Jun 19 (Box 19, Folder 453)
    - Concluding sermon of Lambeth Conference, 1958 Aug 10 (Box 19, Folder 453)
    - Greeting to the Old Barn Conference, 1958 Aug 27 (Box 19, Folder 453)
    - Congratulatory message, 1958 Sep 11 (Box 19, Folder 453)
    - Commendation of General Theological Seminary, 1958 Sep 25 (Box 19, Folder 453)
    - Opening address, General Convention ( The Living Church, 1958 Oct 12), 1958 Oct 5 (Box 19, Folder 453)
    - Broadcast sermon, 1958 Oct 5 (Box 19, Folder 453)
    - Farewell address to General Convention 1958 Oct 14 (transcript from tape) (Box 19, Folder 453)
    - Whitsunday message, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 453)
    - Message re: Lambeth Conference, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 453)
    - "The Church College", 1959 Oct (Box 19, Folder 453)
    - Sermon, 1959 Nov 15 (Box 19, Folder 453)
  - 1960-1972
    - Tribute to the Rt. Rev Raymond Adams Heron ( Church Militant ), 1960 Mar (Box 19, Folder 454)
    - "Bishop Sherrill on Theological Education" (booklet), 1960 (Box 19, Folder 454)
    - "Geoffrey Francis Fisher: An Appreciation" ( The Living Church ), 1961 Mar 28 (Box 19, Folder 454)
    - "A Young Rector in an Old Parish" ( Atlantic Monthly ), 1962 Jul (Box 19, Folder 454)
    - "Leader and Servant" ( The Episcopalian ), 1962 Sep (Box 19, Folder 454)
    - "Small Doubts and Great Decisions" ( The Episcopalian ), 1962 Dec (Box 19, Folder 454)
    - "Edwin Jan van Etten" (booklet), 1963 Oct 20 (Box 19, Folder 454)
    - Speech at dedication of World Council Ecumenical Center, 1964 Jul 11 (Box 19, Folder 454)
    - Sketch of acquaintance with Archbishop Fisher, ca. 1971 (Box 19, Folder 454)
    - Palm Sunday sermon, 1972 Mar 26 (Box 19, Folder 454)
    - Easter message, 1972 Apr 2 (Box 19, Folder 454)
    - Sermon, 1972 Oct 15 (Box 19, Folder 454)
  - Undated, titled sermons, addresses and articles
    - "The Devotional Life of the Minister" (Box 19, Folder 455)
    - "The Effectiveness of the Church" (Box 19, Folder 455)
    - "Here am I; send me" (Box 19, Folder 455)
    - "Leaven and Not Lump" (Box 19, Folder 455)
    - "The Life of the Spirit" (Box 19, Folder 455)
    - "Members One of Another" (Box 19, Folder 455)
    - "Our Times and Eternity" (Box 19, Folder 455)
    - "Up -- Not Down" (Box 19, Folder 455)
    - "Why Go to Church" (Box 19, Folder 455)
    - "Youth. The Colleges. Religion." (Box 19, Folder 455)
    - Statement re: Archbishop Temple (Box 19, Folder 455)
    - Statement at anniversary of Massachusetts General Hospital (Box 19, Folder 455)
    - Statement re: Jews and Christians (Box 19, Folder 455)
    - Sermon for Lay Readers' Convention (Box 19, Folder 455)
    - Untitled (Box 19, Folder 455)
    - Undated, untitled sermons, addresses, and articles (Box 19, Folder 456)
    - Undated messages and prayers (Box 19, Folder 457)
    - Fragments and excerpts (Box 19, Folder 458)
  - Reviews of HKS Books
    - Reviews of William Lawrence: Later Years of a Happy Life (1943) (Box 19, Folder 459)
    - Reviews of The Church's Ministry in Our Time (1949-1950) (Box 19, Folder 460)
    - Reviews of Among Friends (1962) (Box 19, Folder 461)
  - Manuscript of HKS Autobiography
    - Introductory material through page 160 (Box 19, Folder 462)
    - Pages 161 through 383 Index, photographs (Box 19, Folder 463)
    - Holograph draft (Box 20, Folder 465)
- Biographical Documentation, 1900-1986; Series III
  Scope and Contents
  The chronological sequence of this Series is followed by one folder of undated material and eleven oversize scrapbooks which date from 1919 to 1965. Brief descriptions of the material included in each folder or scrapbook are provided.
  - Chronological Sequence
    - Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn, miscellaneous, 1900,1901 (FGS)1903,1906 (HKS) (Box 20, Folder 466)
    - Hotchkiss School, 1906 (Box 20, Folder 467)
    - Hotchkiss School, Yale, 1907 (Box 20, Folder 468)
    - Yale, 1909-1911,1913 (Box 20, Folder 469)
    - Assistant Minister -- Trinity Church, 1914, 1915 (Box 21, Folder 470)
    - Chaplain, Base Hospital No. 6; Rector, Church of Our Saviour, 1917-1920 (Box 21, Folder 471)
    - Certification of Military Service, U.S. Army, 1918 Nov 11-1919 Mar 26 (Box 21, Folder 471A)
    - Marriage to Barbara Harris, 1921 (Box 21, Folder 472)
    - Rector of Church of Our Saviour and calls to Rochester, Chicago, 1921-1923 (Box 21, Folder 473)
    - Rector of Trinity Church, 1923 (Box 21, Folder 474)
    - Rector of Trinity Church and misc., 1924-1927, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 475)
    - Appointment book, 1928 (Box 21, Folder 476)
    - Rector of Trinity Church and election as Bishop-coadjutor of PA, 1928 (Box 21, Folder 477)
    - Appointment book and misc., 1929 (Box 21, Folder 478)
    - Honorary D.D. from Yale, 1929 (Box 21, Folder 479)
    - Appointment book, 1930 (Box 21, Folder 480)
    - Election and consecration as Bishop of Massachusetts, newspaper clippings, 1930 (Box 21, Folder 481)
    - Bishop of MA and misc., 1930-1931, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 482)
    - Diary, 1930 Oct- 1933Jan (Box 21, Folder 483)
    - Appointment book, 1931 (Box 21, Folder 484)
    - General Convention -- Denver; Diocesan Convention, 1931 (Box 21, Folder 485)
    - Miscellaneous, 1932-1933 (Box 22, Folder 486)
    - Election to Yale Corporation and misc., 1934-1935 (Box 22, Folder 487)
    - Appointment book, 1936 (Box 22, Folder 488)
    - Harvard honorary degree and tercentenary, 1936 (Box 22, Folder 489)
    - Trinity College honorary degree and misc., 1936 (Box 22, Folder 490)
    - Diary, 1936 Dec-1940 Dec (Box 22, Folder 491)
    - Appointment book and misc., 1937 (Box 22, Folder 492)
    - Appointment book and misc., 1938 (Box 22, Folder 493)
    - Appointment book and misc., 1939 (Box 22, Folder 494)
    - Appointment book and misc., 1940 (Box 22, Folder 495)
    - General Convention, Kansas City, 1940 (Box 22, Folder 496)
    - Appointment book and misc., 1941 (Box 22, Folder 497)
    - Chairman of Army and Navy Commission: fund-raising trip, 1942 (Box 22, Folder 498)
    - Miscellaneous, 1942 (Box 22, Folder 499)
    - Appointment book, 1943 (Box 23, Folder 500)
    - Trip to Alaska; General Convention; and misc., 1943 (Box 23, Folder 501)
    - Miscellaneous, 1944 (Box 23, Folder 502)
    - Yale Committee on the Relationship of the University and the New Haven Hospital, 1944 (Box 23, Folder 503)
    - Appointment book, 1945 (Box 23, Folder 504)
    - HKS European trip: Enthronement of Archbishop of Canterbury, 1945 (Box 23, Folder 505)
    - HKS European trip: Magazine clippings, 1945 (Box 23, Folder 506)
    - HKS European trip: Newspaper clippings, 1945 (Box 23, Folder 507)
    - HKS European trip: Official papers and typescript material, 1945 (Box 23, Folder 508)
    - HKS European trip: Programs and memorabilia, 1945 (Box 23, Folder 509)
    - Miscellaneous, 1945 (Box 23, Folder 510)
    - Election as Presiding Bishop, 1946 (Box 23, Folder 511)
    - Miscellaneous, 1946 (Box 23, Folder 512)
    - Appointment book, 1947 (Box 23, Folder 513)
    - Honorary degrees and Medal of Merit, 1947 (Box 24, Folder 514)
    - House of Bishops: Winston-Salem, 1947 (Box 24, Folder 515)
    - Installation as Presiding Bishop, 1947 (Box 24, Folder 516)
    - Miscellaneous, 1947 (Box 24, Folder 517)
    - President's Committee on Civil Rights, 1947 (Box 24, Folder 518)
    - President's Committee on Civil Rights, 1947,1948 (Box 24, Folder 519)
    - Tour of Southern dioceses, 1947 (Box 24, Folder 520)
    - Appointment book, 1948 (Box 24, Folder 521)
    - Honorary degrees; Lambeth Conference, 1948 (Box 24, Folder 522)
    - Miscellaneous, 1948 (Box 24, Folder 523)
    - Appointment book, 1949 (Box 24, Folder 524)
    - General Convention, San Francisco, 1949 (Box 24, Folder 525)
    - Honorary degree, University of Edinburgh, 1949 (Box 24, Folder 526)
    - Miscellaneous, 1949 (Box 25, Folder 527)
    - Appointment book, 1950 (Box 25, Folder 528)
    - Founding of Episcopal Church Foundation, 1950 (Box 25, Folder 529)
    - Founding of National Council of Churches, 1950 (Box 25, Folder 530)
    - Miscellaneous, 1950 (Box 25, Folder 531)
    - Commemorative service, St. Paul's Cathedral, London, 1951 (Box 25, Folder 532)
    - Miscellaneous, House of Bishops: El Paso, Protestant Council, 1951 (Box 25, Folder 533)
    - Re: National Council of Churches, 1951 (Box 25, Folder 534)
    - Re: envoy to Vatican, 1951,1952 (Box 25, Folder 535)
    - General Convention, Boston: Magazine clippings, 1952 (Box 25, Folder 536)
    - General Convention, Boston: Newspaper clippings, 1952 (Box 25, Folder 537)
    - General Convention, Boston: Programs and news releases, 1952 (Box 25, Folder 538)
    - Miscellaneous, 1952 (Box 25, Folder 539)
    - Appointment book, 1953 (Box 26, Folder 540)
    - Far East trip, 1953 (Box 26, Folder 541)
    - House of Bishops: Williamsburg, 1953 (Box 26, Folder 542)
    - Miscellaneous, 1953 (Box 26, Folder 543)
    - Anglican Congress, Minneapolis: Magazine and newspaper clippings, 1954 (Box 26, Folder 544)
    - Anglican Congress, Minneapolis: programs and news releases, 1954 (Box 26, Folder 545)
    - Honorary degrees, 1954 (Box 26, Folder 546)
    - Miscellaneous, 1954 (Box 26, Folder 547)
    - Re: change in General Convention site, 1954 (Box 26, Folder 548)
    - World Council of Churches Second Assembly, Evanston: Magazine clippings, 1954 (Box 26, Folder 549)
    - World Council of Churches Second Assembly, Evanston: Newspaper clippings, 1954 (Box 27, Folder 550)
    - World Council of Churches Second Assembly, Evanston: Programs and news releases, 1954 (Box 27, Folder 551)
    - Australia trip, 1955 (Box 27, Folder 552)
    - General Convention, Honolulu: Magazine cllppmgs, 1955 (Box 27, Folder 553)
    - General Convention, Honolulu: Newspaper clippings, 1955 (Box 27, Folder 554)
    - General Convention, Honolulu: Programs and news releases, 1955 (Box 27, Folder 555)
    - Miscellaneous, 1955 (Box 27, Folder 556)
    - Appointment book and miscellaneous, 1956 (Box 27, Folder 557)
    - Russia trip, 1956 (Box 27, Folder 558)
    - World Council of Churches Central Committee Meeting, Hungary, 1956 (Box 27, Folder 559)
    - Appointment book, 1957 (Box 27, Folder 560)
    - House of Bishops, Sewanee, 1957 (Box 27, Folder 561)
    - Miscellaneous, 1957 (Box 27, Folder 562)
    - World Council of Churches Central Committee Meeting, 1957 (Box 28, Folder 563)
    - General Convention, Miami Beach: Magazine clippings, 1958 (Box 28, Folder 564)
    - General Convention, Miami Beach: Newspaper clippings, 1958 (Box 28, Folder 565)
    - General Convention, Miami Beach: Consecration of Edmund Knox Sherrill, 1958 (Box 28, Folder 566)
    - General Convention, Miami Beach: Programs and news releases, 1958 (Box 28, Folder 567)
    - Lambeth Conference, 1958 (Box 28, Folder 568)
    - Miscellaneous, 1958 (Box 28, Folder 569)
    - "Person to Person" TV program, 1958 (Box 28, Folder 570)
    - Retirement tributes, 1958, 1959 (Box 28, Folder 571)
    - World Council of Churches Central Committee Meeting, Nyborg, 1958 (Box 28, Folder 572)
    - Miscellaneous, 1959 (Box 28, Folder 573)
    - World Council of Churches Central Committee Meeting, Rhodes, 1959 (Box 28, Folder 574)
    - Miscellaneous, 1960 (Box 28, Folder 575)
    - World Council of Churches Central Committee Meeting, St. Andrews, 1960 (Box 28, Folder 576)
    - World Council of Churches -- headquarters building fund, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 577)
    - Yale honorary degree, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 578)
    - Yale Medal, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 579)
    - Miscellaneous, 1961 (Box 29, Folder 580)
    - World Council of Churches Third Assembly, New Delhi, 1961 (Box 29, Folder 581)
    - Miscellaneous, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 582)
    - Miscellaneous, 1963 (Box 29, Folder 583)
    - Time Magazine dinner, 1963 (Box 29, Folder 584)
    - Miscellaneous, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 585)
    - Miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 586)
    - World Council of Churches Ecumenical Center, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 587)
    - Dedication of Sherrill Hall, ETS, and misc., 1966 (Box 29, Folder 588)
    - Miscellaneous, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 589)
    - Miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 590)
    - Episcopal Church Foundation dinner, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 591)
    - HKS birthday and consecration anniversary tributes, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 592)
    - Miscellaneous, 1971,1972 (Box 30, Folder 593)
    - Miscellaneous, 1974,1975 (Box 30, Folder 594)
    - General Convention, Minneapolis/St. Paul, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 595)
    - Henry Knox Sherrill Fund, 1976,1977 (Box 30, Folder 596)
    - Miscellaneous, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 597)
    - Miscellaneous, 1977,1978 (Box 30, Folder 598)
    - Miscellaneous, 1979, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 599)
    - Obituaries and tributes, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 674-676)
    - Donation of Henry Knox Sherrill Papers to Yale Divinity Library - Newspaper clippings, 1981 Oct 6 (Box 36, Folder 681)
    - Presentation of HKS's portrait to World Council of Churches - letter, clippings, photos, 1982 Sep (Box 36, Folder 682)
    - Estate of Henry Knox Sherrill - account and letter, 1983 Sep (Box 36, Folder 683)
    - Undated material (Box 36, Folder 677)
    - Miscellaneous material related to BHS, 1918-1986 (Box 36, Folder 684-685)
    - Miscellaneous material related to Sherrill children, 1937-1966 (Box 36, Folder 686)
    - Miscellaneous material related to Sherrill grandchildren, 1937-1966 (Box 36, Folder 687)
    - Article entitled "Henry Knox Sherrill" in Trinity Life, published by Trinity Church, Boston, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 687A)
  - Sherrill Oral History
    - Ault - Herd (Box 40, Folder 728-741)
    - Hobson - Sayre (Box 41, Folder 742-753)
    - Sherman - Turnbull (Box 42, Folder 754 - 762)
    - Walmsey - Wilson (Box 43, Folder 763-766)
  - Oversize Scrapbooks
    - Volume 1 -- Miscellaneous, 1919-1930 (Box Ov20)
    - Volume 2 -- Election as Bishop of Massachusetts, 1930 (Box Ov20)
    - Volume 3 -- Election as Bishop of Massachusetts, 1930 (Box Ov21)